<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pwn on ByteTheCookies</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pwn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pwn on ByteTheCookies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:52:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pwn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CyberSpace CTF 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/cyberspace2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:52:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/cyberspace2024/</guid>
      <description> CyberSpace CTF 2024 Description Get ready to dive into the cyberspace and tackle challenges across categories such as Forensics, Reverse Engineering, Cryptography, Jail, and many more, at https://2024.csc.tf!
Url Discord Performance Summary CTFs: 21/63 Total points: 2032 Position: 83/830 Rating points: ? Writeups Crypto trendy windy trigonity Web ZipZone FeatureUnlocked Trendz (part 1 and 2) Rev Snake </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SekaiCTF 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/sekaictf2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/sekaictf2024/</guid>
      <description>SekaiCTF 2024 Description SekaiCTF is back for its third iteration! This year’s competition will feature various categories designed to test participants’ skills and incentivize learning. Our CTF will have more difficult challenges, and are catered towards intermediate and advanced players—however, there will still be beginner-friendly challenges to welcome players on the newer side.
Url Discord Performance Summary CTFs: 3/34 Total points: 369 Position: 136/1230 Rating points: 2.721 Writeups Rev CrackMe Crypto Some trick PPC (Professional Programming &amp;amp; Coding) Miku vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IdekCTF 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/idekctf2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 12:58:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/idekctf2024/</guid>
      <description> IdekCTF 2024 Description idekCTF is an information security CTF competition organized by the idek team and is aimed at the entire spectrum from high school and university students to experienced players. idekCTF will cover the standard Jeopardy-style CTF topics (binary exploitation, reverse engineering, cryptography, web exploitation, and forensics) as well as other, less standard categories.
Url Discord Performance Summary CTFs: 6/35 Total points: 732 Position: 101/1070 Rating points: 5.405 Writeups Web Hello </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexington Informatics Tournament CTF 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/litctf2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:20:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/litctf2024/</guid>
      <description> Lexington Informatics Tournament CTF Description Lexington Informatics Tournament CTF 2024 is a Jeopardy-style, beginner-friendly online CTF that&amp;rsquo;s open to everyone.
Url Discord Performance Summary CTFs: 18/32 Total points: 2068 Position: 95/830 Rating points: 19.095 Writeups Web Kirbytime </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N00bzCTF 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/n00bzctf2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:26:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/n00bzctf2024/</guid>
      <description> N00bz CTF 2024 Description A 48 hours CTF hosted by n00bz for n00bz. Organized with beginner friendly challenges (and some hard ones), n00bzCTF is dedicated to make cyber security more friendly and approachable for complete n00bz.
Url Discord Performance Summary CTFs: 31/32 Total points: 9794.000 Position: 24/967 Rating points: 24.067 Writeups Web File Sharing Portal Misc Waas </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>